





Summary

Jump to Section

Aconsummate Innovation Specialist, with over 2 decades of experience in leveraging strategic approach in leading large engagements across IT, Administration & Systems Engineering, Strategy Formulation and People Management

Outstandingly skillful in establishing CXO level relationships to develop strategies that convey a customized approach to all business needs & improvement plans

Pioneered business negotiations with both Govt. & Private sector companies

Work Experience | Education |

Proven skills in developing & executing business expansion initiatives and setting processes for delivering customercentric solutions

Excellent people manager with strong skills in building high performing teams that excel in delivering business value with high morale & low attrition

Contributed as Head for IT Services at Premier Foods LLC in Dubai Airport Free Zone, Dubai; administered entire operations for over 20 Operating Offices all over the world, most located in West Africa and GCC

Work Experience

MEMG Securities Ltd as Sub-Broker

Jun 2014 to Jun 2020

B2B Excellence, Business Relationship Management, Business Management & Expansion, Team Management ~

Key Result Areas:

Leading strategic game changer transformational B2B functions entailing sourcing and maintaining relationships with franchisees and Business Associates for MEMG Securities; championing these initiatives in collaboration with various teams

Establishing roadmap for enhancing operations to achieve global standards

Identifying & replicating best practices across all functions and re-structuring Business Model & Operating Model in line with changing business needs

Strategically establishing & improving policies for business expansion through market analysis, competitor analysis, projected financials and investment plans

Collaborating with top clients of the franchisees and keeping them engaged in the markets

Guiding & mentoring teams to improve operations and achieve cost savings

Delivering process breakthrough improvements towards business excellence by adopting business process improvement techniques and ensuring quality compliance

Danish & Co as Manager

Feb 2011 to Mar 2014

Supply Chain Management, Material Management, Process optimisation, Customer Interaction, Project Management ~

Key Result Areas:

Headed the overall responsibilities as Manager for Interior Decorators and Supply Chain for building material in Bengaluru, Frazer Town

Designed interior as per client's requirement including supplying of building material and carpentry work Projects Undertaken:

Important

 Using Free CV Search you have access to featured candidate profiles of Naukri. You can browse through the profiles and email the candidates of your choice directly using the email option provided. To prevent misuse of candidate information, contact details and attached resume of the candidates have been withheld Asus Technologies - Bengaluru Toyota Tsusho Insurance Broker Pvt. Ltd., Bengaluru

Premier Foods LLC as IT Manager

Feb 2004 to Feb 2011

Business Continuity Planning, Business Risk Assessment, Information Security Management, ERP Solution Infrastructure Deployment ~

Highlights

Contributed as Head for IT Services at Premier Foods LLC in Dubai Airport Free Zone, Dubai; administered entire operations for over 20 Operating Offices all over the world, most located in West Africa and GCC

- Successfully worked on
- o Windows 2003, Exchange, SQL and MS Great Plains (Implementation Under Progress)
- o NetlQ Mail Marshall for Exchange server 2003
- Cipher Trust's IronMail 6.1.1 Appliance for email traffic filtering

Implemented backup and disaster recovery strategy using Veritas Solution

Successfully developed report to list out stock quantity by product code or stock group

Headed Information Security responsibilities including Firewall and VLAN deployment, firewall failover implementation and Backup Solutions

Managed full functional ERP Solution Infrastructure deployment including SQL Server and Network Infrastructure and configuration of IIS on Windows 2003 server for the front-end of the application

Executed the configuration of remote desktop connection for the users to logging in to the server for various application levels fine tuning

Monitored the installation of thin Print / Client Software for printing facility on network printers on the remote end of RDC

Installed & managed full functional Videoconferencing H.320 and Networks, Video over IP and the Internet. Video Conferencing Products of Polycom & Motion Media

- o ViewStation FX (Poylcom)
- o ViewStation EX (Polycom)
- o VSX3000 (Polycom)
- MM745 (Motion Media)

^ Back to Top

Education

UG: B.Com (Commerce) from Bangalore University in 1994

^ Back to Top

Languages Known

Language	Proficiency	Read	Write	Speak
english				
hindi				
kannada				
Urdu				

^ Back to Top

Affirmative Action

Work Authorization

Category: General
Physically Challenged: No

Job Type: Permanent
Employment Status: Full time

^ Back to Top

Careers - About Us - Clients - Terms & Conditions - FAQ's - Contact Us - Report a Problem - Site Map - Resources
Our Partners: Jeevansathi Matrimonials - ICICIcommunities.org - 99acres - Real Estate In India
All rights reserved © 2021 Info Edge India Ltd.

Careers - About Us - Clients - Terms & Conditions - FAQ's - Contact Us - Report a Problem - Site Map - Resources
Our Partners: Jeevansathi Matrimonials - ICICIcommunities.org - 99acres - Real Estate In India
All rights reserved © 2021 Info Edge India Ltd.